onlyfinance.com 2006-12-21

# OnlyFinance Privacy Policy

Only Finance is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. 

_Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as once you use our website and/or our product and/or account aggregation services ("Services") you will be regarded as having read and accepted this Privacy Policy. You must not use our website or our Services if you do not accept this Privacy Policy._

**The information we collect**

We will collect personal information about you which you give to us when you register to use our account aggregation service and when you provide information as part of our product aggregation service, for example, in order to obtain a quote for a secured loan. The provision of the Services to you may also require us to store details of your transactions, together with details of your financial information. We will periodically review your personal information to ensure that we do not keep it for longer than is necessary. 

**Purposes for which we use information about you**

We may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  1. to enable you to access and use the Services; and/or 
  2. to personalise aspects of our overall service to you; and/or 
  3. to communicate with you; and/or 
  4. to process a transaction between you and a third party.

**Passing on information about you**

Please be aware that once you use our website or our Services, you will be regarded as having given your consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties:

  1. Third party providers whose products or services are listed on the results pages of the channels on our website, for the purposes of obtaining an online quotation for you or comparing different products and services as requested by you;  

  2. The Financial Services Authority and/or other regulatory/governing bodies for the purposes of compliance monitoring; 
  3. Other third parties that might be able to offer, either an alternative product in the event that your preferred choice of third party provider does not approve your application or offers a less attractive product or service than you had originally applied for, or simply a product that meets the basic criteria of the type of product for which you have searched on OnlyFinance.com.

**Third party providers and data privacy**

If you decide to enter into a contract with a third party provider through a channel on our website, the information you have provided to us together with any further information requested by, and supplied by you to, the third party provider will be held by the provider for the purposes set out in that provider's privacy policy. Therefore, you are strongly advised to read your chosen provider's privacy policy and satisfy yourself as to the purposes for which the provider will use your personal information before entering into the contract. We have no responsibility for the uses to which a provider puts your personal information once you have contracted with that provider. 

**Advertisements**

The advertisements that you see displayed on this website are delivered on our behalf by a third party advertising company. No personal data for example your name, address, email address or telephone number are used during the course of serving our advertising, but, on our behalf, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. This cookie does not collect personal data about you nor is it linked to any personal data about you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please click here [http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy ](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy)

**Security**

The internet is not a secure medium. However we have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy. Firewalls are used to block unauthorised traffic to the servers and the actual servers are located in a secure location which can only be accessed by authorised personnel. We also keep your information confidential. Our internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information. 

**Cookies**

We use cookies. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. They allow us to understand what areas of the website are of interest to our visitors and allow us to provide a better user experience. These cookies do not track individual user information, and all our cookie data is encrypted and cannot be read by other websites. It is possible to 'turn off' the cookies in your browser and this will not affect the functionality of the web site. You can find out more information about cookies including how to switch cookies on or off i.e. accept or refuse cookies from [ www.aboutcookies.org ](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

Transferring your information abroad 

Information supplied by you to us will only be transferred abroad by us or our agents for the purpose of performing contractual obligations to you, or when you have given your prior consent to such transfer. 

**Your Rights**

You have certain rights under the Data Protection Act 1998. For example, we will always let you have a copy of all personal information we have about you should you request it. We may charge you a fee for a copy of such information.
